Joseph Stephen Cullinan Collection, 1895-1939
University of Houston Libraries
- Box List
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1916 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1917 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1917 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1918 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1919 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "D" (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "E" (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "F" (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "G" (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "H" (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "I" (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, "J" (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Houston - Port Arthur Railway Co. - General Correspondence, 1925-26 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Houston - Port Arthur Railway Co. - General Correspondence, 1927-28 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Houston - Port Arthur Railway Co. - Annual Meetings, 1925-33 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Concerning Houston Northshore Railway Line, 1925-26 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - General Correspondence, 1912-1916 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - General Correspondence, 1922-25 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - Floating Equipment, 1915-1916 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1915-1916 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - Financial Records, 1912-15 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - Financial Records, 1916-1917 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Southern Transportation Co. - Organization, 1914-1916 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Insurance, 1914-1915 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Insurance, 1916 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Liability Insurance, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - T.P. Lee's Records, 1914-1916 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Employment Applications, 1914-1916 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Salutes to Gulf Oil, 1915 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Financial Reports, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Oil Tests, 1914-1916 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Pipeline Department Drilling Process, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Real Estate, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Real Estate, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Right of Way, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Humble and East Houston Stations, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Railway Spurs, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Telephone and Telegraph Leases, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Production Reports, October - December, 1915 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Production Reports, 1914- September 1915 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Production Reports, January - March, 1916 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Farmer's Production Co. - Production Reports, April - June, 1916 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Taxes, Codes and Refining Process, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Humble Field Reports, July 1915- Feb. 1916 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Humble Field Reports, July 1915- Feb. 1916 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Producing Dept., Cottages and Pipe, 1914-16 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Production Runs, 1914-16 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Texas Oil Prospects, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Tankage, 1914-16 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Texas Oil Prospects, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Texas Oil Prospects, 1915 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Texas Oil Prospects, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Oklahoma and Louisiana Oil Prospects, 1914-16 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Miscellaneous Locations, 1914-16 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Daily Stock Reports, East Houston, May - Dec., 1915 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Daily Stock Reports, East Houston, Jan. - June, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Daily Stock Reports, Humble, July - Dec., 1915 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Daily Stock Reports, Humble, Jan. - June, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Royalties, 1914-16 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Accounting; Banking and Financing; Leases - Burt & Griffith (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Leases - Miscellaneous; Leases - Matagorda Co.; Oil Sales - General Policy (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Claims and Suits, 1915-16 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Wharf Permit, 1915-16 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Co. - Company Reorganization, 1915-16 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Intracoastal Canal Association - Anti-St. Lawrence Seaway Material, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Intracoastal Canal Association, May-July, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Intracoastal Association, August - December, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Intracoastal Canal Association, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Intracoastal Canal Association, 1936-37 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Accounts, December 1934-July 1935 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Accounts, August 1935 - May 1936 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Accounts, June 1931- December 1936 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - J.S. Cullinan: Instruction on Correct Business Procedures, 1919-20 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - American Republics Corporation: Special Investigation of West, 1924-1925 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - American Republics Corporation: Re-Organization Proceeding, undated material (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceeding, 1925-1926 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, 1927 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, 1928 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, Jan. - Aug., 1932 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, September, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, October, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, Jan. - April, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, May, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, June - July, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, August 1933 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, September, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, October, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, November, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, December, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, January 1934 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, Feb., 1934 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, March 1934 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, April - Dec., 1934 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, Jan. - April, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, May - August, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, September, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings, Oct. - Dec., 1935 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - American Republics Corporation: Reorganization Proceedings,, 1936 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Pasadena Farm - General Monthly Accounts, 1911-1913 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Pasadena Farm - Miscellaneous Accounts of Production and Consumption, 1912-1913 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Pasadena Farm Payroll Accounts, 1912 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Pasadena Farm Payroll Accounts, 1913 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Pasadena Farm Inventories, 1911-1912 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Maps Concerning Pasadena Farm (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Maps Concerning Pasadena Farm (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence Concerning Car, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Concerning Car, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, E.E. Morrison, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, E.E. Morrison, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, A-Z, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, A-Z, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, A-Z, 1923-28 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Cullinan Family Correspondence, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Cullinan Family Correspondence, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, W.T. Sinclair, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, E.E. Morrison, Jan. - June, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, E.E. Morrison, July-December, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Business Papers, A-Z, 1916 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Business Papers, B-C (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Loans and Loan Applications, D-M (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Loans and Loan Applications, D-M (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Loans and Loan Applications, P-W (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Federal Investment Co., Norsworthy Property, 1915-1917 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Federal Investment Co.; Freestone Lands, 1915-1916; Miscellaneous, 1915-1916; Miscellaneous Business Letters, 1916 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Fidelity Trust Company: Organization - Offices, employees, etc; Meetings - Directors, etc.; Offices, Equipment, Rules, etc. (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Fidelity Trust Company, Stocks - USR and Imp. Co.; Stocks- Misc.; Stock Deposits;Reinvestments; Marketing Securities (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Fidelity Trust Company, Financial Statements; Real Estate; Tax Matters; Trust Department (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Sharp-Hughes Tool Co., 1912-1913 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Sharp and Hughes Tool Co., Statements; Minutes and Meetings; Union Tool Contract; Lucy Contract (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Sharp Estate, 1903-1913 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Sharp Estate, 1903-1913 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Mrs. W.B. Sharp, Personal, 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. W.B. Sharp, Personal, 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: K-M, 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: K-M, 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: N-Q, 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: N-Q, 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: R-T (1 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: R-T (2 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: R-T (3 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: U-Z (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: U-Z (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence re Securities, Bonds, Financial Statements, etc., 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence re Securities, Bonds, Financial Statements, etc., 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence re Securities, Bonds, Financial Statements, etc., 1914-1916 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, re Bonds, Securities, Dividends, Financial Statements, etc., 1916-1918 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, re Bonds, Securities, Dividends, Financial Statements, etc., 1916-1918 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records and Business Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1914-1918 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Houston Ship Channel, Undated or Peculiarly Dated (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Houston Ship Channel, Undated or Peculiarly Dated (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1916-1917 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1916-1917 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1918-1919 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1918-1919 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1920-1924 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1925-1930 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1925-1930 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1931-1933 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1934-1936 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Houston Ship Channel, 1934-1936 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Raywood Canal and Mining Company, 1912-1920 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Raywood Canal and Mining Company, 1912-1920 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Hardy Mining Company, 1915-1922 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Hardy Mining Company, 1915-1922 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Old River Company, 1914-1916 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Cumbe Mining Company, 1914-1916 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, "A" (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, "B" (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, "B" (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, "C" (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, "C" (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, "C" (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, "G" (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, "H" (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, "H" (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, "H" (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, "I-J" (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, "I-J" (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, "J" (Jones, Jesse H.) (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, "K" (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, "K" (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, "L" (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, "L" (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, "M" (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, "M" (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, "M" (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, "N-O" (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - The Waco Record - B.G. McKie; More Money or a National Moratorium, 7/15/32 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Credit and Currency, 1 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Credit and Currency, 2 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Credit and Currency, 3 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Credit and Currency, 4 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Credit and Currency, 5 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Credit and Currency, 6 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Credit and Currency, 7 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Credit and Currency - Clippings and Pamphlets, 1 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Credit and Currency - Clippings and Pamphlets, 2 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Credit and Currency - Clippings and Pamphlets, 3 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Credit and Currency - Clippings and Pamphlets, 4 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Credit and Currency - Clippings and Pamphlets, 5 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Credit and Currency, Pamphlets, 6 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Facts Pertaining to Credit, 1931-1933 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, United Venezuela Oil Company, 1935-1937 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Cherokee Mining Company - Incorporation and Legal Opinions (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Cherokee Mining Company - Financial Records (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Cherokee Mining Company - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1925-1937 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Cherokee Mining Company - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1925-1937 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - The State Money Association, 1929-1930 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - United Veterans - B.E.F. [Bonus Expeditionary Forces] (1 of 2) (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - United Veterans - B.E.F. [Bonus Expeditionary Forces] (2 of 2) (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Bank Failures in the U.S., 1893-1933 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, Pamphlets (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, Pamphlets (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Maya Corporation - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1926-1928 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Maya Corporation - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Maya Corporation - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Maya Corporation - Stock, January - June, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Maya Corporation - Stock, July, 1926-1936 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Maya Corporation - Holding Company, 1925-1926 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Maya Corporation - Holding Company, 1925-1926 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Maya Corporation - Securities, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Maya Corporation - Smith vs. J.S. Cullinan, et al., 1929-1933 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Maya Corporation - Smith vs. J.S. Cullinan, et al., 1929-1933 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Maya Corporation - Smith vs. J.S. Cullinan, et al., 1934-1937 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Maya Corporation - Smith vs. J.S. Cullinan, et al., 1934-1937 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1925-1927 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1925-1927 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1928-1929 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1928-1929 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1928-1929 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Maya Corporation - Litigation, 1930-1933 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Photo Documentation File for Collection (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - 1 through 7 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - 8 through 15 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - 16 through 27 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - 28 through 39 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - 40 through 46 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - 47 through 58 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - 59 through 71 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - 72 through 81 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - 82 through 89 A (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - 90 through 100 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - 101 - 110: See Photo Documentation File For Collection, 102 - 104 Offset (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - 111 through 120 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - 121 through 133 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - 134 through 143 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - 144 through 153 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - 154 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - 155 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - 156 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - 157 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - 158 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - 159 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - 160 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - 161 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - 162 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - 163 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - 164 through 179 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - 180 through 189 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - 190 through 198 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - 200 through 213 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - 214 through 224 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - 225 through 238 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - 239 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - 240 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - 241 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - 242 through 253 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - 254 through 270: See Photo Documentation File for 261-264, 269, 270 (Offset) (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - 271 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - 272 and 272 A (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - 273 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - 275 through 277: See Photo Documentation File for 274 (Offset) (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - Pedigrees and Tabulated Records, J.S. Cullinan (Box 69, Folder 1)